<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2021 on Home</title>
    <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2021 on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 21:52:01 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Install Digikam in Truenas Jail</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/06/09/install-digikam-in-truenas-jail/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 21:52:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/06/09/install-digikam-in-truenas-jail/</guid>
      <description>1 - Create new jail Use Web GUI or CLI to create a new jail according to your liking.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to do it via Web GUI with NAT and NAT Port Forwarding enabled.
I&amp;rsquo;ll also add a port mapping for ssh from jail&amp;rsquo;s tcp port 22 to host&amp;rsquo;s 22222.
2 - Get ports Connect to the newly created jail so we can fetch and extract ports:
iocage console digikam portsnap fetch portsnap extract 3 - Install dependencies At this point, it might be worth to install xauth which will be required to start digikam via ssh with X11 Forwarding enabled and vim to edit few config files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Photoprism in Truenas Jail</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/06/05/install-photoprism-in-truenas-jail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 17:18:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/06/05/install-photoprism-in-truenas-jail/</guid>
      <description>For quite a while I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for a self-hosted photo &amp;amp; video gallery.
I tried things like:
 NextCloud   OwnCloud   Piwigo   Lychee    Yet, none of them made the cut.
Then, I came across this Ask HN: Alternatives to Google Photos?  thread on Hacker News. I checked out self-hosted projects mentioned in this comment  .
Photoprism  got my attention as it offers automatic image classification based on Google TensorFlow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Converting raw Nikon NEF files to DNG and back on Linux</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/02/05/converting_raw_nikon_nef_files_to_dng_and_back_on_linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/02/05/converting_raw_nikon_nef_files_to_dng_and_back_on_linux/</guid>
      <description>Regardless of whether it makes sense or not to convert raw files to DNG, you might choose a middleground solution and embed the original raw file in a DNG file.
The major drawback to this solution is that the resulting DNG file will be roughly double in size when compared with the original raw file.
The benefit of emdedding a raw files in a DNG file that you can easily extract it later on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
