<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2021 on Home</title>
    <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2021 on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 11:43:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to resolve Pytest: Cell Var From Loop</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/12/07/how-to-resolve-pytest-cell-var-from-loop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 11:43:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/12/07/how-to-resolve-pytest-cell-var-from-loop/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I came across following pylint warning:
$ pylint test.py ************* Module test test.py:29:28: W0640: Cell variable sort_key defined in loop (cell-var-from-loop) ------------------------------------------------------------------ Your code has been rated at 9.41/10 (previous run: 9.41/10, +0.00) Here&amp;rsquo;s an example code snippet that triggered such warning:
&amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34;Replace lambda with operator.itemgetter to sort List[dict] by dict key.&amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34; import itertools from typing import Dict, List def parse_raw_message(msg: str) -&amp;gt; Dict[str, str]: &amp;#34;&amp;#34;&amp;#34;Parse a pipe-delimited message into a key:value pairs &amp;amp; skip empty keys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix an issue with incorrectly transferred files via GSConnect</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/09/25/fix-file-transfers-for-gsconnect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 22:09:22 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/09/25/fix-file-transfers-for-gsconnect/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve recently flashed LingeageOS 18.1 onto my phone. After rooting it, I&amp;rsquo;ve installed my fav firewall app AFWall&amp;#43; . But since then I was having problems with sending files to my pc or other phones via (GSConnect app)[https://github.com/GSConnect/gnome-shell-extension-gsconnect]. All sent files had different size than the original file on my phone. I&amp;rsquo;ve described it in this bug report comment .
After a bit of reading I realised that I have to add some extra iptables rules described in GSConnect&amp;amp;rsquo;s Wiki ,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use default factory to initialize nested dataclass fields</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/09/15/initialize_nested_dataclasses_with_default_factory/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 17:50:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/09/15/initialize_nested_dataclasses_with_default_factory/</guid>
      <description>I you happen to work with nested Python dataclasses , then maybe you&amp;rsquo;ve noticed an issues with defining field values by creating an instance of some object.
In the example below, all instances of class Main will point to the same instance of class Sub:
from dataclasses import dataclass, field @dataclass class Sub: prop: str = field(default=&amp;#34;some value&amp;#34;) @dataclass class Main: sub: Sub = Sub() m1 = Main() m2 = Main() id(m1) Out[1]: 140304747921264 id(m2) Out[2]: 140304748528400 assert id(m1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Digikam in Truenas Jail</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/06/09/install-digikam-in-truenas-jail/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 21:52:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/06/09/install-digikam-in-truenas-jail/</guid>
      <description>1 - Create new jail Use Web GUI or CLI to create a new jail according to your liking.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to do it via Web GUI with NAT and NAT Port Forwarding enabled.
I&amp;rsquo;ll also add a port mapping for ssh from jail&amp;rsquo;s tcp port 22 to host&amp;rsquo;s 22222.
2 - Get ports Connect to the newly created jail so we can fetch and extract ports:
iocage console digikam portsnap fetch portsnap extract 3 - Install dependencies At this point, it might be worth to install xauth which will be required to start digikam via ssh with X11 Forwarding enabled and vim to edit few config files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Photoprism in Truenas Jail</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/06/05/install-photoprism-in-truenas-jail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 17:18:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/06/05/install-photoprism-in-truenas-jail/</guid>
      <description>For quite a while I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for a self-hosted photo &amp;amp; video gallery.
I tried things like:
NextCloud OwnCloud Piwigo Lychee Yet, none of them made the cut.
Then, I came across this Ask HN: Alternatives to Google Photos? thread on Hacker News. I checked out self-hosted projects mentioned in this comment .
Photoprism got my attention as it offers automatic image classification based on Google TensorFlow. I gave it a spin by following Getting started instructions for Docker Compose .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Converting raw Nikon NEF files to DNG and back on Linux</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/02/05/converting_raw_nikon_nef_files_to_dng_and_back_on_linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 09:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2021/02/05/converting_raw_nikon_nef_files_to_dng_and_back_on_linux/</guid>
      <description>Regardless of whether it makes sense or not to convert raw files to DNG, you might choose a middleground solution and embed the original raw file in a DNG file.
The major drawback to this solution is that the resulting DNG file will be roughly double in size when compared with the original raw file.
The benefit of emdedding a raw files in a DNG file that you can easily extract it later on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
