<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>general on Home</title>
    <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/categories/general/</link>
    <description>Recent content in general on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 18:08:50 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kowalcj0.github.io/categories/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Books worth reading</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/general/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 18:08:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/general/books/</guid>
      <description>Book reading stats In May 2020, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to keep track of my reading habits.
Below are simple reading stats.
 Completed per year:   2020: 3  Total number of completed books: 3  Po Polsku  Absurd Everestu  by: Denis Urubko  (orig. Абсурд Эвереста)  meta  published: 2013  genres: biography, mountaineering  completed: 2020-06-05  links:     Words/Idioms/Terms:  zrejterować - wycofać się, zrezygonować, uciekać, brać nogi za pas dworować sobie z kogoś - szydzić, wyśmiewać się z kogoś, drwić, odnosić się z pogardą somnambuliczny - lunatyczny sybaryta - człowiek, który spędza czas na przyjemnościach i uwielbia zbytek; hedonista, epikurejczyk, wygodniś jumar - urządzenie sportowe umożliwiające przemieszczanie się po pionowo przymocowanej linie    Genialni  by: Mariusz Urbanek   meta  published: 2014  genres: history, biography, science, mathematics  completed: 2020-05-27  links:      Quotes:  David Hawkins, żegnając przyjaciela, napisał: &amp;ldquo;Ludzie, którzy żyją tylko trochę, tylko trochę umierają.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Articles worth reading</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/general/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 16:56:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/general/articles/</guid>
      <description>A while ago I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered Wallabag  . It&amp;rsquo;s a self hostable application for saving web pages. It extracts the article&amp;rsquo;s content and can automatically tag it with matching label. Basically it&amp;rsquo;s an open-source competitor of Pocket  , Instapaper  or Evernote  .
Fetching a list of all entries via Wallabag&amp;amp;rsquo;s API  is very easy. And with a help of jq  you can transform it into a simple JSON file which you can use to populate a Hugo Data Templates  .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies worth watching</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/general/movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 11:59:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/general/movies/</guid>
      <description>Below you&amp;rsquo;ll find some movies that I particularly like. Some of the them are available on Amazon Prime Video  or mubi.com  .
AFAIK most of the titles below are not available on Netflix.
Great movie lists If you looking for something interesting to watch have a look at those lists:
 iMDB: Top 250   iMDB: Top 100 Greatest Movies of All Time (The Ultimate List)   iMDB: Top 50 spanish movies   MUBI: Top 1000   MUBI: 30 must see Japanese film classics   MUBI: Top 50 Japanese films   MUBI: Top Indian films    Recent and fairly recent     Title Director Genres Year Links Comments    1917 Sam Mendes Drama, War 2019       Amazing long takes  The Gentleman Guy Ritchie Action, Comedy, Crime 2019         Bacurau Kleber Mendonça Filho, Juliano Dornelles Weird Western 2019       Imagine Tarantino going on holidays to Brazil just to make a movie about human hunting as a sport combined with some references to The Magnificent Seven and to Brazilian social banditry legends (Cangaço).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>