<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>general on Home</title>
    <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/categories/general/</link>
    <description>Recent content in general on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 19:54:20 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kowalcj0.github.io/categories/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quotes, mottos &amp; adages - Cytaty, motta i powiedzenia - 2020</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2020/10/05/quotes-mottos-adages-cytaty-motta-powiedzenia-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 19:54:20 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2020/10/05/quotes-mottos-adages-cytaty-motta-powiedzenia-2020/</guid>
      <description>A bunch of my favourite quotes, mottos &amp;amp; adages I&amp;rsquo;ve accrued over time.
In English  I&amp;rsquo;ve had a lot of worries in my life, most of which never happened. &amp;ndash; Mark Twain 💪💪💪💪💪💪 There are three sides to every story: yours, mine, and the truth and no one is lying. &amp;ndash; Anonymous 💪💪💪 Change is the only constant. &amp;ndash; Unknown Change begets change as much as repetition reinforces repetition. &amp;ndash; Bill Drayton The shortest path to oneself leads around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books worth reading</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/general/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 18:08:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/general/books/</guid>
      <description>Book reading stats In May 2020, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to keep track of my reading habits.
Below are simple reading stats.
 Completed per year:   2020: 4  Total number of completed books: 4  In English  Unthinkable  by: Helen Thompson   meta  published: 2018  genres: psychology, science Completed on 2020-08-08 Completed on 2020-08-08   completed: 2020-08-08  links:     Quotes:  Life without memory is not life at all&amp;hellip; Our memory, is our coherence, our reason our feeling, even our action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Articles worth reading</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/general/articles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 16:56:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/general/articles/</guid>
      <description>A while ago I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered Wallabag  . It&amp;rsquo;s a self hostable application for saving web pages. It extracts the article&amp;rsquo;s content and can automatically tag it with matching label. Basically it&amp;rsquo;s an open-source competitor of Pocket  , Instapaper  or Evernote  .
Fetching a list of all entries via Wallabag&amp;amp;rsquo;s API  is very easy. And with a help of jq  you can transform it into a simple JSON file which you can use to populate a Hugo Data Templates  .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies worth watching</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/general/movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 11:59:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/general/movies/</guid>
      <description>Below you&amp;rsquo;ll find some movies that I particularly like. Some of the them are available on Amazon Prime Video  or mubi.com  .
AFAIK most of the titles below are not available on Netflix.
Great movie lists If you looking for something interesting to watch have a look at those lists:
 iMDB: Top 250   iMDB: Top 100 Greatest Movies of All Time (The Ultimate List)   iMDB: Top 50 spanish movies   MUBI: Top 1000   MUBI: 30 must see Japanese film classics   MUBI: Top 50 Japanese films   MUBI: Top Indian films    Recent and fairly recent     Title Director Genres Year Links Comments    La Haine  Mathieu Kassovitz Crime, Drama 1995       One of the best french movies I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen  Malèna  Giuseppe Tornatore Romantic, Comedy, Drama 2000          Pandorum  Christian Alvart SciFi, Horror, Action &amp;amp; Adventure 2006       A must see for all Alien series lovers  Django Unchained  Quentin Tarantino revisionist Western 2012         Beasts of the Southern Wild  Benh Zeitlin Adventure, Drama, Fantasy 2012          The best offer Watched on 2021-01-28 Watched on 2021-01-28    Giuseppe Tornatore Psychological thriller 2013          Free State of Jones  Gary Ross Action, Biography, Drama 2016         The Red Turtle  Michaël Dudok de Wit Animation, Family, Fantasy 2016         The Handmaiden  Chan-wook Park Drama, Romance, Thriller  2016         November  Rainer Sarnet Drama, Fantasy, Horror 2017       A gloomy &amp;amp; murky Estonian movie with fantastic camera work  The Bar  Álex de la Iglesia Black Comedy, Thriller 2017          The Square  Ruben Östlund Satire, Drama 2017         The Nightingale  Jennifer Kent  Adventure, Drama, Thriller 2018         A female Django Unchained!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
