<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pa11y on Home</title>
    <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/tags/pa11y/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pa11y on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 22:56:03 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kowalcj0.github.io/tags/pa11y/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automatically Delete Old Pa11y Results From MongoDB</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2020/06/06/automatically-delete-old-pa11y-results-from-mongodb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 22:56:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2020/06/06/automatically-delete-old-pa11y-results-from-mongodb/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve probably already noticed that Pa11y-Dashboard runs all the tasks on a daily basis. If you have a lot of tasks (e.g. 100+) then the test results can fairly quickly gobble up your MongoDB quota (if you have any).
If your MongoDB has a size limit defined, then you can do two things:
 manually delete old test results or use TTL Index to do it for you automagically  MongoDB supports TTL indexes  since v2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Proxy Requests to Pa11y Webservice Hosted on Heroku</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2020/06/04/how-to-proxy-requests-to-pa11y-webservice-hosted-on-heroku/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 13:39:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2020/06/04/how-to-proxy-requests-to-pa11y-webservice-hosted-on-heroku/</guid>
      <description>Pa11y-Dashboard runs of top of Pa11y Webservice  (WS).
By default Pa11y WS listens on port 3000 and Pa11y Dashboard listens on port 4000.
Unfortunately Heroku doesn&amp;rsquo;t allow its users to easily expose multiple ports per application.
To overcome this limitation, I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to make Pa11y-Dashboard proxy requests to WS via /ws/ endpoint.
After a bit of searching I&amp;rsquo;ve found a dedicated proxy module for expressjs called express-http-proxy  .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Pa11y Dashboard on Heroku</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2020/06/03/run-pa11y-on-heroku/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 19:57:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2020/06/03/run-pa11y-on-heroku/</guid>
      <description>To run Pa11y Dashboard on Heroku, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to:
 add puppeteer buildpack  to your dyno pass --no-sandbox argument to Chrome  Puppeteer buildpack will install Chrome and all dependencies required to run it in headless mode.
Second step is only necessary if you&amp;rsquo;re going to see following error when running Pa11y tests on Heroku:
Failed to launch chrome! No usable sandbox! Update your kernel or see https://chromium.googlesource.com/chromium/src/+/master/docs/linux_suid_sandbox_development.md for more information on developing with the SUID sandbox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add Basic Auth to Pa11y</title>
      <link>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2020/06/02/add-basic-auth-to-pa11y/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 16:33:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kowalcj0.github.io/2020/06/02/add-basic-auth-to-pa11y/</guid>
      <description>Pa11y  is a great open sourced automated accessibility testing tool.
It uses headless Chrome browser and HTML_CodeSniffer  as test runner.
Unfortunately out of the box Pa11y Dashboard  doesn&amp;rsquo;t come with any form of authentication. This might be OK for some people, but in our case we&amp;rsquo;re going to add basic-auth to it.
This short tutorial is based on pa11y-dashboard v3.1.0.
Enter http-auth I&amp;rsquo;ve selected http-auth  package to do the job as it&amp;rsquo;s a popular and actively maintained package.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
